<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Jonah Brüchert -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>ch.openboard.OpenBoard</id>
  <name>OpenBoard</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">OpenBoard</name>
  <summary>Interactive whiteboard for schools and universities</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Cuadro blanco interactivo para escuelas y universidades</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Interaktiv tavle for skoler og universiteter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Quadro branco interativo para escolas e universidades</summary>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-only</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <developer_name>Département de l'Instruction Publique (DIP-SEM)</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>OpenBoard is an open source cross-platform teaching software for interactive whiteboard designed primarily for use in schools and universities. It can be used both with interactive whiteboards or in a dual-screen setup with a pen-tablet display and a beamer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">OpenBoard es un software de enseñanza de plataforma cruzada de código abierto para cuadros interactivos diseñado principalmente para uso en escuelas y universidades. Se puede utilizar con marcos interactivos o en una configuración de pantalla dual con un monitor de escritorio gráfico y un proyector.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">OpenBoard er et kryssplattform og åpen kildekode undervisningsprogram for interaktive tavler, spesielt designet for bruk i skoler og universiteter. Det kan brukes både med interaktive tavler eller i et dobbelt skjermoppsett med tegnebrett med skjerm og projektor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O OpenBoard é um software de ensino de plataforma cruzada de código aberto para quadros interativos projetado principalmente para uso em escolas e universidades. Ele pode ser usado com quadros interativos ou em uma configuração de tela dupla com um monitor de mesa gráfica e um projetor.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.openboard.ch</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/OpenBoard-org/OpenBoard/issues</url>
  <url type="help">http://openboard.ch/support.en.html</url>
  <url type="translate">https://github.com/OpenBoard-org/openboard/pulls</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <update_contact>jbb_AT_kaidan.im</update_contact>
  <translation type="qt">OpenBoard</translation>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">ch.openboard.OpenBoard.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Board mode</caption>
      <image type="source">https://www.imgload.org/images/openboard-screenshot134104bf2845eb1fc.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Web browser</caption>
      <image type="source">https://www.imgload.org/images/openboard-screenshot2dcbcb955dabe8967.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>File browser</caption>
      <image type="source">https://www.imgload.org/images/openboard-screenshot3558eae6a8b145d09.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <metadata>
    <value key="GnomeSoftware::popular-background">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/ch.openboard.OpenBoard/master/ch.openboard.OpenBoard-thumb.png</value>
  </metadata>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release type="stable" date="2019-04-10" version="1.5.3">
      <description>
        <p>New Features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support of OpenSSL 1.1 has been added on the three supported platforms. A special thanks to super7ramp for his help</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bug fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Some scaling issues could be experienced while exporting a document to PDF format</li>
          <li>An image could be lost after a page duplication followed by the deletion of the image on one of the two pages</li>
          <li>An image could be lost after the duplication of a page in Documents Mode</li>
          <li>When duplicating grouped objects of different types, the z-order was not preserved</li>
          <li>Perform "Set As Tool" on a flash animation could result on a crash</li>
          <li>Secured web pages was not loading on Windows internal navigator</li>
          <li>Slashes were allowed in folder's names</li>
          <li>Ukrainian translation's file extension is now uk, instead of ua. A special thanks to glixx for reporting it</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Known issues:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The redesign of the Documents mode was a complex development and several small cosmetic bugs may still remain, including focus issues</li>
          <li>Some slow motion can be experienced in macOS while using drag and drop in the new document tree structure</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="stable" date="2019-01-22" version="1.5.2"/>
    <release type="stable" date="2018-12-13" version="1.5.1"/>
    <release type="stable" date="2018-11-29" version="1.5.0"/>
  </releases>
  <provides>
    <binary>openboard</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
